# Ambuj Dubey (Full Stack Developer)

ambujdubey89@gmail.com (+91) 9753750955 www.linkedin.com/in/ambuj-dubey-2923b456 https://github.com/ambujbpl Address:- CM-78 Indore

# **Summary of Qualifications**

Dedicated and efficient full stack developer with 3+ years experience in the application layers, presentation layers, and databases. Played major role with high-level proficiency in the following technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js, SQL, MongoDB, Angular JS and React JS. I am very familiar and experienced with Web Application Architecture, have worked with a good number of successful development teams and provide the ability to work by taking complete ownership of tasks.

# **Work Experience**

Full-Stack Developer (July 2019 to present)

Logikview Analytics, MPSEDC IT Park Electronics Complex, Indore. 452010

## **Key Qualifications & Responsibilities**

- Collaborates with development team which includes Product Manager, Software Engineer and Quality Assurance team to identifying software problems, testing methods, and best solutions.
- Developed full-stack applications which processed, analyzed, and rendered data visually.
- Integrated app-based solutions with databases, file systems, and cloud-based systems.
- Object-Oriented Analysis.

Junior Full Stack Developer (June 2018-June 2019)

Ideata Analytics, MPSEDC IT Park Electronics Complex, Indore. 452010

#### **Key Qualifications & Responsibilities**

- Developed software applications with technologies like Nodejs, Strapi, Express.js and integration with REST APIs for ADFS services, live tracking application and other services.
- Managed, optimized, and updated databases as necessary.
- Collaborates with development team and create testing methods.
- Object-Oriented Analysis and Relational Database Systems.
- Testing the designed unit test case.

Software Developer (November 2017 - May 2018)

**Green Ticks Bhopal 462026** 

#### **Key Qualifications & Responsibilities**

- Developed full-stack applications which processed, analyzed, and rendered data visually with technologies like Nodejs, Express.js Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap3.
- Studied, evaluated, and proposed solutions to complex architectural challenges for the purpose of introducing new features.

# Software Engineer (October 2016 - October 2017)

# Mobigesture Software Pvt. Ltd. Banjara Hills, Hyderabad

# **Key Qualifications & Responsibilities**

- Developed app-solutions using a variety of languages, frameworks, and platforms such as Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap3 SQL, and HTML.
- UI-Design and Development of Source code.
- Responsive Web Design (Bootstrap framework).

# **Key Skills**

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, PHP.
- Bootstrap
- Node JS
- Angular IS
- React JS
- SQL Databases
- MongoDB

# **Academic Qualification**

P G Diploma	C-DAC Hyderabad 2016 batch
M. Tech	Digital Communication RGPV Bhopal 2015
B.Tech	Electronics & Telecommunication RGPV Bhopal 2011
12 <sup>th</sup>	Mathematics M.P. Board 2007
10 <sup>th</sup>	M.P. Board 2005

## **Personal Profile**

Father's Name	Mr. Shravan Dubey		
Mother's Name	Mrs. Kalpana Dubey		
Date of Birth	06-08-1989		
Nationality	Indian		
Languages Known	English, Hindi		
Hobbies	Internet Surfing and sports activities.		
Permanent Address	20-A Sachchidanand Nagar, BHEL, Bhopal (M.P.)		
Skills and Proficiencies	Creative, Team Work, Willingness To Learn		

# **Declaration**

T 1 1.		1 11	. C	1 - 1		of my knowledge.
Indrant	7 MACIATA THA	t the intermatic	n fiirnichde	I anova ic trii	α τα τηα ηαςτ	οτ μιν συσινίμασα
ILLICIO	ucciai c uia	t tilt illitti illatit	iii iui iiisiict	i above is u u	c to the best	. Of the Knowicusc.

Place: Indore (M.P.)

Date: (Ambuj Dubey)